{"items": [{"question": "expressed or understood without being said directly", "answer": "tacit", "options": ["secretive", "tacit", "tight lipped", "taciturn"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "close mouthed", "answer": "tight lipped", "options": ["taciturn", "secretive", "tight lipped", "laconic"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Habitually reserved and uncommunicative", "answer": "taciturn", "options": ["secretive", "taciturn", "laconic", "laconia"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Inclined to secrecy or reticence about divulging information", "answer": "secretive", "options": ["laconia", "secretive", "laconic", "loquacious"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Brief and to\u00a0the\u00a0point", "answer": "laconic", "options": ["laconic", "loquacious", "laconia", "laconicism"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "An ancient region of southern Greece, dominated by Sparta", "answer": "laconia", "options": ["laconicism", "laconia", "loquacious", "eloquent"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Full of trivial conversation", "answer": "loquacious", "options": ["magniloquence", "laconicism", "eloquent", "loquacious"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A neatly short and concise expressive style of expression", "answer": "laconicism", "options": ["eloquent", "laconicism", "magniloquence", "inarticulate"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Speaking readily, clearly, and effectively", "answer": "eloquent", "options": ["garrulous", "eloquent", "magniloquence", "inarticulate"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "High-flown style; excessive use of verbal ornamentation", "answer": "magniloquence", "options": ["garrulous", "inarticulate", "magniloquence", "banal"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Without or deprived of the use of speech or words", "answer": "inarticulate", "options": ["inarticulate", "banal", "garrulous", "verbose"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Full of trivial conversation", "answer": "garrulous", "options": ["garrulous", "verbose", "banal", "voluble"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Repeated too often; overfamiliar through overuse", "answer": "banal", "options": ["verbose", "banal", "voluble", "cogent"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Using or containing too many words", "answer": "verbose", "options": ["verbose", "voluble", "cogent", "vociferous"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Marked by a ready flow of speech", "answer": "voluble", "options": ["voluble", "cogent", "uncommunicative", "vociferous"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Powerfully persuasive", "answer": "cogent", "options": ["cogent", "uncommunicative", "vociferous", "reticent"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Conspicuously and offensively loud", "answer": "vociferous", "options": ["uncommunicative", "vociferous", "reticent", "reserved"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Not inclined to talk or give information or express opinions", "answer": "uncommunicative", "options": ["uncommunicative", "reserved", "soliloquy", "reticent"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Temperamentally disinclined to talk", "answer": "reticent", "options": ["reserved", "reticent", "soliloquy", "ventriloquy"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Marked by self-restraint and reticence", "answer": "reserved", "options": ["ventriloquy", "colloquial", "reserved", "soliloquy"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Speech you make to yourself", "answer": "soliloquy", "options": ["soliloquy", "ventriloquy", "colloquial", "circumlocutory"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The art of projecting your voice so that it seems to come from another source", "answer": "ventriloquy", "options": ["circumlocutory", "ventriloquy", "offspring", "colloquial"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Characteristic of informal spoken language or conversation", "answer": "colloquial", "options": ["colloquial", "offspring", "progeny", "circumlocutory"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Roundabout and unnecessarily wordy", "answer": "circumlocutory", "options": ["circumlocutory", "progeny", "magnanimous", "offspring"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The immediate descendants of a person", "answer": "offspring", "options": ["offspring", "magnet", "magnanimous", "progeny"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The immediate descendants of a person", "answer": "progeny", "options": ["magnanimous", "magnificent", "progeny", "magnet"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "generous in forgiving an insult or injury", "answer": "magnanimous", "options": ["magnitude", "magnet", "magnanimous", "magnificent"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A characteristic that provides pleasure and attracts", "answer": "magnet", "options": ["magnitude", "magnet", "magnificent", "magnum"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Extraordinarily good or great", "answer": "magnificent", "options": ["magnum", "magnum opus", "magnitude", "magnificent"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "The property of relative size or extent (whether large or small)", "answer": "magnitude", "options": ["verbatim", "magnitude", "magnum opus", "magnum"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "A large wine bottle for liquor or wine", "answer": "magnum", "options": ["magnum", "magnum opus", "verbatim", "verbiage"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "A great work of art or literature", "answer": "magnum opus", "options": ["verbatim", "verbiage", "volva", "magnum opus"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Using exactly the same words", "answer": "verbatim", "options": ["verbatim", "revolve", "verbiage", "volva"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "The manner in which something is expressed in words", "answer": "verbiage", "options": ["verbiage", "revolve", "volva", "revolution"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Cuplike structure around the base of the stalk of certain fungi", "answer": "volva", "options": ["revolution", "volva", "contrary", "revolve"], "answer_index": 2}, {"question": "Turn on or around an axis or a centre", "answer": "revolve", "options": ["disciplinary", "contrary", "revolution", "revolve"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "A drastic and far-reaching change in ways of thinking and behaving", "answer": "revolution", "options": ["disciplinary", "stationary", "revolution", "contrary"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Very opposed in nature, character or purpose", "answer": "contrary", "options": ["contrary", "imaginary", "stationary", "disciplinary"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Relating to discipline in behaviour", "answer": "disciplinary", "options": ["imaginary", "commentary", "stationary", "disciplinary"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Standing still", "answer": "stationary", "options": ["imaginary", "commentary", "involve", "stationary"], "answer_index": 4}, {"question": "Not based on fact; unreal", "answer": "imaginary", "options": ["commentary", "evolve", "imaginary", "involve"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "A written explanation or criticism or illustration that is added to a book or other textual material", "answer": "commentary", "options": ["evolve", "involve", "commentary", "tacit"], "answer_index": 3}, {"question": "Engage as a participant", "answer": "involve", "options": ["involve", "tight lipped", "evolve", "tacit"], "answer_index": 1}, {"question": "Undergo development or evolution", "answer": "evolve", "options": ["tacit", "evolve", "taciturn", "tight lipped"], "answer_index": 2}], "title": "Word power Made Easy - Session 24 to 26.txt", "total": 44}